http://www.dms-magnetics.com/privacy.htm

MicroSense 53005000 Series Probes
MicroSense 6800 SeriesMicroSense MiniSensors for Vacuum EnvironmentsMicroSense 6360MicroSense SpinCheckApplications Selector
PositioningDistance & DisplacementRun OutThicknessAutofocus & NullingVibration
Solar Wafer Thickness MetrologyVibrating Sample Magnetometer (VSM)
EZ VSMModel 10 Vibrating Sample MagnetometerTorque MagnetometerVSM Options and Accessories
Magnetic Metrology
Polar Kerr for MRAMKerrMapperDiskMapper H7Polar Kerr for PMR Disk
Dimensional Wafer Metrology Systems
UltraMap-C200UltraMap-APBPUltraMap-200B
Capacitive Position Sensors Support
Capacitive Sensor CalibrationCapacitve Position Sensor Export InformationObsolete Product Information
VSM SupportMagnetic Metrology SupportDimensional Wafer Metrology Customer SupportTerms and Conditions
Capacitive Position Sensors Resources
White Papers and Tech NotesProduct Data SheetsUser Guides and Manuals
VSM Resources
Downloads
Magnetic Metrology Resources
Capacitive Position Sensors Sales ContactsVSM Sales Contacts
Contact Us FormVSM Contacts and Representatives
Magnetic Metrology Sales ContactsDimensional Wafer Metrology Sales ContactsFactoryProcurement
KLA
Who We Are
Management Team
Press Releases
Privacy PolicyThis Privacy Policy covers how MicroSense, LLC, (known as “MicroSense”) treats Personal Information (as defined below) that MicroSense collects and receives through your use of MicroSense websites. By using the MicroSense Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information in accordance with the terms of this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy Only Applies to MicroSenseThis Privacy Policy does not apply to the practices of companies that MicroSense does not own or control, or to the people that MicroSense does not employ or manage.Children’s Privacy PolicyThe MicroSense Site is not intended for use by any children, including children under the age of thirteen. MicroSense does not knowingly collect Personal Information online from children under thirteen. If you think that MicroSense has collected Personal Information from your child, please contact us at webmaster@microsense.net (or the address provided below). Because MicroSense is committed to protecting children’s privacy online, use of the MicroSense Site by children under the age of thirteen is prohibited.Collection of Personal Information“Personal Information” is information about you that is personally identifiable, like your name, address, email address or phone number, and that is not otherwise publicly available. MicroSense collects Personal Information in a number of circumstances, including under the following circumstances: Registrations: To use certain features of the MicroSense Site, you must first complete a form which requires you to provide certain Personal Information, such as your name and email address (providing demographic information, such as your job title, is optional). We keep this registration information on file with any information you've already given us on previous visits to the MicroSense Site. MicroSense collects this information and uses it internally for purposes such as marketing, customer support and administration, technical administration of the MicroSense Site, or to contact you.Purchases and Information: You may order e-mail newsletters or purchase MicroSense products or services. Personal Information collected by MicroSense is often limited to e-mail address, language, country or location, but may include other information. For example, if you choose a service or transaction that requires payment, such as making a purchase in the shopping area of the MicroSense Site, we or our third party service providers will request Personal Information necessary for billing and/or shipping, such as: name, address, telephone number, and credit card number.Other: MicroSense may, from time to time, collect other information from you when you voluntarily provide it (for instance, when we conduct surveys). Information collected by these means is used internally for purposes such as marketing, customer administration, technical administration of the MicroSense Site, or to contact you.Use and Security of Personal InformationIn addition to the uses described above, we may use your Personal Information for the following purposes:To make the MicroSense Site easier for you to use by not making you enter your Personal Information more than once.To respond to your inquiries and to deliver services that you request or purchase and to provide you with related customer service.To help us create and publish content and offers most relevant to you.To send administrative information to you, such as information regarding the MicroSense Site and changes to our terms, conditions and policies.To send you marketing communications that we believe may be of interest to you.As we believe to be necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public and government authorities, including public and government authorities outside your country of residence; (d) to enforce our terms and conditions; (e) to protect our operations or those of any of our affiliates; (f) to protect our rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of our affiliates, you or others; and (g) to allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain.For our business purposes, such as data analysis, audits, fraud monitoring and prevention, developing new products, enhancing, improving or modifying our products and services, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and operating and expanding our business activities. MicroSense strictly protects the security of your Personal Information and honors your choices for its intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration, or destruction.MicroSense takes precautions to protect our users’ information both online and offline. Inside MicroSense, data is stored in password-controlled servers with limited access.We seek to use reasonable organizational, technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information within our organization. Unfortunately, no data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that your interaction with us is no longer secure (for example, if you feel that the security of your account has been compromised), please immediately notify us in accordance with the “Contact Us” section below.Your Personal Information may be transferred to countries other than your own to process and store data in accordance with our Privacy Policy and to provide you with products and services. Some of these countries may not have the same data protection safeguards as the country where you reside. By using the MicroSense Sites, you consent to us transferring your data to these countries. Personal Information SharingMicroSense does not rent, sell or share your Personal Information with other people or non-affiliated entities except to provide the products or services you’ve requested, when MicroSense has your permission, or under the following circumstances.We provide the information to trusted third parties who work on behalf of MicroSense or with MicroSense under confidentiality agreements, including third parties answer customer questions about products or services, send postal mail, process event registrations and provide other administrative services. These third parties may use your Personal Information to help MicroSense communicate with you and for other reasons. However, these third parties do not have any independent right to share your Personal Information. MicroSense also works with other vendors, partners, advertisers and other service providers in different industries and categories of business. This may include other companies who wish to offer our registered customers information about their products and services using postal mail. For more information regarding these third parties, please contact us at one of the Webmaster email addresses below.MicroSense may disclose your Personal Information if required to do so by law, including laws outside your country of residence, or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on MicroSense; (b) protect and defend the rights, property, privacy or safety of MicroSense, our affiliates, you or others; or (c) allow us to pursue available remedies or limit the damages that we may sustain; or otherwise in response to law enforcement requests (including requests from authorities outside your country of residence).In the event that MicroSense is acquired by or merged into another company, or if MicroSense undergoes any reorganization, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of its business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings), all information collected will be transferred to the acquiring company as one of MicroSense's assets and will be governed by the acquiring company's privacy policy, if any.Control of your Personal InformationWhen you register, or otherwise give us Personal Information, MicroSense will not share that information with third parties without your permission, other than as stated in this Privacy Policy.We will provide you with the means to ensure that your Personal Information is correct and current. You may request the Personal Information you have provided to us at any time, contacting the webmaster at the address below to change your marketing preferences.Please note that we may need to retain certain information for recordkeeping purposes and/or to complete any transactions that you began prior to requesting a change or deletion. There may also be residual information that will remain within our databases and other records, which will not be removed.Visiting the MicroSense Site and Use of CookiesMicroSense collects information from all users of the MicroSense Site, except as described below. What information MicroSense collects and how we use it, depends upon your activity on the MicroSense Site.MicroSense and its service providers collects non-personally identifiable information from all visitors to the MicroSense Site, such as IP address, browser type, and the date and time a user accessed the MicroSense Site. We use this information for system administration purposes in order to enhance the operation of the MicroSense Site and make it more useful to visitors. MicroSense uses cookies. A cookie is a small amount of data placed on your computer or device. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie terminates automatically after you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your computer or device, but can be removed by following the directions on your browser and/or mobile operating system. You can set your browser to disable cookies, but this may prevent you from enjoying all of the features of the MicroSense Site.We use cookies to deliver content that is specific to your interests, to streamline the login process, and to collect anonymous user traffic data. The cookies make your use of the MicroSense Site easier, may allow you to retrieve an earlier shopping cart, make the MicroSense Site run more smoothly, and help us to maintain the security of the MicroSense Site. We also use cookies to understand how the Site is used so that MicroSense can improve the Site and resolve questions about it.If you choose to not have your browser or device accept cookies from the MicroSense Site, you will be able to view the text on the screens, however you will not experience a personalized visit nor will you be able to subscribe to the service offerings on the MicroSense Site. Your Shopping Cart will also not remember items added but not checked out. We may use pixel tags (also known as web beacons and clear GIFs) to, among other things, track the actions of users of the MicroSense Site (including email recipients), measure the success of our marketing campaigns and compile statistics about use of the MicroSense Site and response rates.We use the Google AdWords remarketing service on the MicroSense Sites to advertise on third party websites (including Google) to previous visitors to those MicroSense Sites. It could mean that we advertise to previous visitors who haven't completed a task on our Sites, for example using the contact form to make an enquiry. This could be in the form of an advertisement on the Google search results page, or a site in the Google Display Network. Third-party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on someone's past visits to the website. Of course, any data collected will be used in accordance with our own privacy policy and Google's privacy policy. You can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page, and if you want to you can opt out of interest-based advertising entirely by cookie settings or permanently using a browser plugin.We may use and disclose information that does not personally identify you for any purpose, except where we are required to do otherwise under applicable law. In some instances, we may combine such information with Personal Information. If we do, we will treat the combined information as Personal Information as long as it is combined.MicroSense also collects Personal Information from users of the MicroSense Site as described further above.Notification of Changes to this Privacy PolicyMicroSense may occasionally update this Privacy Policy. When we do, we will also revise the Privacy Policy Version Date at the top of the Privacy Policy. Any changes will become effective when we post the revised Privacy Policy on the MicroSense Sites. Your continued use of the MicroSense Sites after such changes have been posted shall constitute your assent to be bound by these changes.Contact UsYou may use the contact information below if you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Policy or your dealings with the MicroSense Sites. Webmaster:MicroSense, LLC205 Industrial Avenue EastLowell, MA USA 01852Email: webmaster@microsense.net
Why MicroSense
|
About Us
|
Products
|
Customer Support
|
